[
  {
    
      "QuestionID": 1,
      "Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
      "option1": "Quit",
      "option2":"Remove",
      "option3":"Abolish",
      "option4":"Replace",
      "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    
    "QuestionID": 2,
    "Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
    "option1": "Quit",
    "option2":"Remove",
    "option3":"Abolish",
    "option4":"Replace",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    
    "QuestionID": 3,
    "Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
    "option1": "Quit",
    "option2":"Remove",
    "option3":"Abolish",
    "option4":"Replace",
    "Answer": 1
},
{
  
  "QuestionID": 4,
  "Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
  "option1": "Quit",
  "option2":"Remove",
  "option3":"Abolish",
  "option4":"Replace",
  "Answer": 2
},{
    
  "QuestionID": 5,
  "Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
  "option1": "Quit",
  "option2":"Remove",
  "option3":"Abolish",
  "option4":"Replace",
  "Answer": 1
},
{

"QuestionID": 6,
"Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
"option1": "Quit",
"option2":"Remove",
"option3":"Abolish",
"option4":"Replace",
"Answer": 2
},{
    
  "QuestionID": 7,
  "Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
  "option1": "Quit",
  "option2":"Remove",
  "option3":"Abolish",
  "option4":"Replace",
  "Answer": 1
},
{

"QuestionID": 8,
"Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
"option1": "Quit",
"option2":"Remove",
"option3":"Abolish",
"option4":"Replace",
"Answer": 2
},{
    
  "QuestionID": 9,
  "Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
  "option1": "Quit",
  "option2":"Remove",
  "option3":"Abolish",
  "option4":"Replace",
  "Answer": 1
},
{

"QuestionID": 10,
"Question": " Find the synonym, Derogue",
"option1": "Quit",
"option2":"Remove",
"option3":"Abolish",
"option4":"Replace",
"Answer": 2
}
]